

in ☑ 🗘 🌐





PROFILE

I am currently a student of a triple degree Master Program in Image Processing and Computer Vision. I am very keen in different fields Compuer Vision, in which I have more than 3 years of experience. I am currently looking for an opportunity to write my master thesis.

LANGUAGES

English: professional

proficiency

German: conversational

Hungarian: native **Spanish**: beginner

EDUCATION

Erasmus Mundus Masters in Image Processing and Computer Vision

PPCU, Budapest Hungary UAM, Madrid, Spain Ubx, Bordeaux, France http://ipcv.eu/

2019 - Present

Molecular Bionics Engineering B.Sc

PPCU, Budapest Hungary

2015 - 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack developer

MODIT zrt.

Digitization of Hungarian Adaptation System in Java **EE** and Angular

Research Intern

Feb. 2018 - Jan. 2019

June 2019 – Jan. 2020

SZTAKI (Institute for Computer Science and Control)

Working at Machine Perception Research Laboratory as a part of a medical image processing project, classed zMed.

SKILLS

Python Matlab C++ OpenCV Keras Latex self learning and management teamwork change management and problem solving · strategic thinking

PROJECTS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

FaceQNet: Quality assessment system for facial recognition in deep learning framework

3D Scene Reconstruction through Multiple Images **Object Detection and Tracking**

3D Reconstruction of the Hepatic Vessels

